(Raj:)It looks like a map
from Dungeons & Dragons.
(Amy:)Mm.
(Howard:)Except the creature in the crib
is a level-nine poop monster.
(Raj:)Okay, uh, you check
for squeaks,
(Raj:)and I will
mark them down.
(Bernadette:)Okay.
(Howard:)Space A-3, here we go.
(Howard:)It's squeaking. Mark it.
(Raj:)It's nice to think that
you grew up in this room
(Raj:)and now your daughter's
going to as well.
(Howard:)Mm. I hope she has the same
amount of sex in it I did.
(Howard:)None. Next square.
(Raj:)Why do you bounce with your
hands in the air like that?
(Howard:)It's a tradition of my people.
♪ If I were a rich man ♪
"Material Girl"
needs to be retired.
(Raj:)That is your karaoke song.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to play
a driving game I invented?
(Leonard:)Is it about the failing state
of my relationship with Penny?